♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
♪ Get me down ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot show yourself ♪
♪ Gypsy I'm not ready ♪
♪ Tom Servo hello there ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors shutting)
(laughing)
- Hi everyone, welcome
to the satellite of love,
I'm Mike Nelson,
this is Crow T. Robot
and that's Tom Servo.
We're just roughhousing.
- Gee, it looks
like fun you guys.
- Well, truly not that much
fun, hop down there, buddy.
(grunting)
- That's hilarious.
- Hey guys, this
is not a gymnasium.
- Oh, come on Gyps,
it's fun when it's fun.
- Yeah, fun until somebody dies.
- Whoa, that's harsh, huh?
- I think it's time for
you to go for a ride.
- Oh, no, no, please.
- Oh, come on, it's fun!
Isn't it fun?
It's fun.
(group chattering)
(crying)
- Good one, Mike.
- We'll be right back.
- [Tom] My Mom says you
have to go home now.
(adventurous music)
- [Tom] Uh-uh, uh-uh.
- Come on, Tom, you just
drop, we'll catch ya.
- [Tom] But I'm scared.
- Oh, don't be
ridiculous, come on.
- [Tom] Okay, here I come.
(screaming)
(coughing)
- We can't have
nice things, can we?
- [Tom] Help me, Mike, help me.
- I'm coming.
- It'll have to wait, the
dual airbags are calling.
- Bonjour, my little friends.
I must admit I'm
giddy with excitement.
You see Frank and I
have invented the first
really real time machine.
Previously time machines have
been mere works of fiction.
But this, this is
good, this is real.
Isn't that right, Frank?
- That's right,
we've broken through
the space-time continuum and
passed the savings on to you.
- It's quite
complicated actually,
but all you need to know
is we get into the capsule
and are transported
back thousands of years,
back to caveman times.
Bonjour!
- [Frank] That's right, we're
heading back through time
at a dizzying speed.
Oh, boy, look,
we're in the 60's,
a time of tumultuous change.
- [Dr. Forrester] Frank,
I've spotted a T-bird.
We must be in the 50's.
- [Frank] Oh, no, now
its the 40's, the 40's.
- [Mr. Forrester]
That's why I'm busy
planting my victory garden.
- [Frank] Back, back we go.
Oh, hi, Alexander Graham Bell.
- [Dr. Forrester] Farther
back still, Wyatts,
and look, Kit Carson, Frank.
Boy, it sure is weird
being in the old west.
Are you dressed yet?
- [Frank] No.
- [Dr. Forrester] We
seem to have entered
some kind of strange
time porthole thingy.
Allow me to shout back
through the centuries
back to you, Nelson!
- Fabio
- We're Fabio.
- That's right,
we are all Fabio,
star of book covers, movies
and marketer of his own
line of chest grease.
- And why are we all Fabio?
Because everyone
wants to be Fabio.
Men respect Fabio.
Women love Fabio.
- There isn't a
female organism alive
that doesn't worship Fabio.
Even Janice knows.
- We believe Fabio
is here to stay
and that's why we've come
up with the Fabio kit.
The jutting manly, yet
accessible jaw line
and this soft mane
of grabable hair.
And the tan, taut,
muffin-y chest.
Fabio fever, catch it!
(singing)
- Hey, you guys look like Fabio.
(laughing)
- Hey, don't laugh, we're Fabio.
- Big buttery slabs of Fabio.
- Ahh, she's gone, let it go.
Back to you guys, hey!
- Well, Mike, as you
can see I went back,
all the way back
to caveman times
where I got very
close to the world's,
Frank!
How come I'm dressed
like a caveman
and you're dressed like a,
whatever you're supposed to be.
It's all going to hell.
- Well, I guess that
leaves it to me,
Telvisio Frankus to tell you
that your experiment today
is Outlaw, starring the
very hugable Jack Palance.
The anvil that
men do lasts long.
The ghoul is often
furred in their homes.
I'll send you the movie.
- Ahh, movie time!
(doors opening)
- [Mike] Fabio, Fabio.
- [Tom] Waylon Conrad presents.
(laughing)
- [Mike] They make such a
production out of everything
but it's limited,
thank goodness.
- [Crow] John
Norman's Steak-ateria.
- [Mike] With Jane Russell?
- [Crow] Oh please, oh
please, oh please, oh please.
- [Mike] Oh no, don't
get your hopes up.
Oh, that's Italian
for Adrian Barbeau.
- [Crow] I hate
this movie already.
- [Tom] Me too.
- [Mike] Give it a chance.
Hey, I have Donna
Denton pajamas.
- [Tom] I think you
mean Doctor Denton.
- [Mike] Oh, you're right.
I crap bigger than this movie.
(laughing)
- [Tom] This lush score, though.
- [Mike] Oh, the great Amish
director of photography.
- [Tom] Ah, yes, featured in the
New York Times book
review, I believe.
- [Crow] Who requested
the names be shown
at the crescendo of
the musical score?
- [Tom] Harry Alan Towers!
- [Mike] Now you see, you
really undermine your authority
when you put "Bud" in
the middle of your name.
Huh, Joe Namath!
- [Crow] She's got
her legs on wrong.
Oh no, no, no, no, she doesn't.
- [Mike] He's wearing one of
those Fred Flintstone ties.
- [Tom] Swing and a miss.
- [Mike] Wayne
Gretzky, the great one.
- [Actor] Hey, you
doing anything later?
- [Crow] Yeah, blowing you off.
- [Actor] Kevin,
this is a surprise.
- [Crow] Someone
who'll talk to me.
- [Actor] Past your
bedtime, isn't it?
- [Actor] Better to be
in bed early than alone.
- [Crow] You're sweet.
- [Mike] It's Doc Savage.
- [Actor] Stick
around, stick around.
Would you check out
the legs on that blonde
at the end of the bar?
She is awesome.
- [Tom] That's my brother, man.
- [Actor] Well I'm a ladies man,
I love 'em, I love 'em.
- [Tom] I am so heterosexual.
- [Actor] Hey, would
you lighten up?
What's wrong?
- [Crow] I don't
have a crispy shirt.
- [Actor] What is with you?
How come I don't see you
go out with any women?
- [Tom] I'm my own woman.
- [Actor] What are
you, my mother?
- [Actor] Hey, come here, baby.
- [Tom] He's a treasure.
- [Actor] Is that your friend?
(whirring)
- [Crow] It's Commissioner
Gordon calling.
- [Mike] Later in
Millard's Crossing.
- [Tom] Previously on Outlaw.
- [Actor] Where the hell am I?
- [Tom] You're the hell here.
- [Actor] You've come
to a land called Gor.
Gor is a harsh world and
she breeds harsh people.
- [Tom] But the
rents are reasonable.
- [Actor] We believe
you've been sent to us
through the stone.
- [Crow] Two months salary.
- [Tom] Oh, and we don't
believe in transitions.
- [Crow] Honey, I
shrunk the Nelson.
- [Actor] That's
not our mountains.
- [Crow] That's where Buddy
Hackett and Jack Carter
got their start.
- [Tom] Wanna hand
me a magazine?
What the?
- [Actor] People of Gor.
- [Tom] An ancient
motivational speaker.
- [Actor] Have returned.
- [Tom] Maybe it's another
world that's a dream.
- [Crow] This is
some weird stuff.
(groaning)
- [Mike] No more
gin fizzes for me.
- [Watney] Hey baby,
what's your sign?
Yield?
- [Mike] See, I'm guessing
the crispy guy in the middle
is gonna go home, put on
a pan of mac and cheese
and fall asleep.
- [Tom] Oh sure, the red onion
will solve all your problems.
- [Watney] No, no,
we'll party, Kevin.
You know how to party.
Well look, my luck can't
be any worse over there
than it is over here, come on!
- [Crow] Hmm, the
Pullman is located
in the Russian Parliament.
- [Watney] We'll use
your car, save me gas.
- [Cabot] We always use my car.
- [Watney] Picky, picky.
- [Cabot] I'll
drop you off, okay?
- [Tom] Ohh, will
I drop you off.
- [Mike] I worry about
a superhero named Kevin
who drives a Camaro.
- [Actor] What is that thing?
One of those mood
rings or something?
- [Cabot] Oh this
is a long story.
I ordered off Pete Rose.
- [Tom] Hey, can we
listen to Z-Wack.
- [Actor] No one backs
up like the outlaw.
- [Crow] Hey, your Playboy
air freshener thing
dropped on the floor.
- [Mike] Hey, back at ya pal.
- [Tom] I hope he puts in
his eight track of Aqualung.
- [Watney] What the hell's the
matter with the car, Kevin?
Whoa, whoa, keep it on the road.
- [Crow] It's just the
stagehand's last day.
- [Tom] Once I get
up to 90 it'll stop.
When time traveling, always
wear your seat belts.
- [Mike] You think
there's any chance
Barney Rubble there could
go through the windshield?
- [Crow] Sorry folks, we
simply could not afford
to have special effects.
(singing a tune)
- [Tom] Oh, they're in Ishtar.
- [Mike] Todo, I have a feeling
this isn't the red onion.
- [Crow] He's a mouth
breather, that one.
- [Watney] Cabot,
Cabot, you okay?
Cabot, speak to me, you alright?
Cabot, what the hell's going on?
Where the hell's the car?
- [Actor] I thought you had it.
- [Crow] We have worm sign.
- I can't believe it.
- [Tom] The things I can
do with my spinal graft.
- I can't believe it.
I'm back, I am back, I am back.
- [Tom] And better than ever.
- [Watney] Back where?
- [Talena] This is
where Talena lives.
- [Watney] Who's Talena?
- [Cabot] Talena,
my girl, my love.
This is the plante
of Gor, Gor, Gor!
- [Watley] What the hell's Gor?
- [Tom] It's the hell here.
- Listen Cabot, what
are you talking about?
Where the hell are we?
What's going on here, Cabot?
- [Crow] Shh, I'm acting.
- I must go to Koruba.
- What?
- Koruba!
- [Watney] Same to you.
Cabot, Cabot, listen
to me, what's going on,
what happened last night?
(chanting "kill him")
Cabot, listen, would
you speak to me?
I want to go home right
now, alright, Cabot?
Where you going?
No, no, wait, Cabot, show me
what the hell's going on here.
- [Tom] Cabot, no one would see
if you killed him right now.
- [Crow] They'd probably
give him a free drink
at the Pullman.
- [Watney] Cabot,
would you wait up?
- [Tom] Hey, Cabot.
I'm a bad boy.
- [Watney] Cabot,
it's getting hot.
- [Mike] This would be
a good drinking game.
Every time he says Cabot
you could take a drink.
- [watney] Cabot, Cabot, Cabot,
can we just hold it a minute?
- [Tom] Shh, he's conducting
the Flight of the Bumble Bee.
- [Cabot] We're getting close.
- [Watney] Getting
close to where?
- [Crow] The Perkins on 494.
- [Watney] Koruba?
Hey, are there any
women on Koruba?
- [Tom] Yeah, and
they'll reject you too.
- [Watney] You still
remember women, don't ya?
- [Crow] Sand nazis,
I hate these guys!
- [Mike] Wouldn't it be great
if you were stuck
in another dimension
with an annoying guy
and he brought beer?
- [Watney] Cabot!
(shouting)
(adventurous music)
- [Tom] Oh, I'm doing my best
here, it's all this sand.
I wanna go back to the Pullman.
- [Crow] Yes, it's T.
Lawrence, night at the Pullman.
- [Tom] I am confident
that I am secure.
You, you sit and you stay.
- [Crow] They're
wearing dance belts.
- [Tom] Well I hope you like it,
oh, hey, I was trying to play!
- [Mike] Sold with a
gel pack and a stunt man
all for $1.25.
- [Crow] Hey, did Rick say
you could use his
sword to kill us?
- [Tom] Oh, he should've
set his purse down.
- [Mike] Hey, thanks for
setting up my stunt man.
Oh, stunt misfire.
Stinky pit.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] He's all
yours, take him.
- [Crow] Yes, take
him, take him.
Hey, it's a gallon bike tights.
Bludgeoning the sand.
- [Tom] You are in
such trouble young man.
- [Crow] I'm a monge.
- [Actor] Through the home
stone I have succeeded
and Cabot is here on Gor.
- [Tom] Wow, his
lips don't even move.
- [Actor] The casino
has acquired much power
and hungers for more.
- [Tom] Ta-da.
- What are you doing?
- [Crow] Drying my
hands, then the towels.
- I have been
cleaning and adjusting
the vibrations of
the home stone.
- And I'm out of Pine Sol.
- [Tom] Well, she's all yours.
If it's cold just
keep the peddle down
when you start it up.
Have fun.
- [Crow] Hmm, what do you know,
he crapped bigger than me.
- [Tom] Hey Crow, I think I know
where you're going with that,
and enough, let's stop there.
Yes, but is it art?
Go ahead and touch it, go ahead.
Ahh, the Golden
days, before sewers.
Hey Buffy and Jody.
We come over to the Jericho
once a year for this sale.
- [Crow] It's Iowa!
- [Mike] Oh for crying out loud.
Staying at a Red Roof Inn.
- [Tom] Oh, this
shovel is heavy.
- [Crow] He's got a
Jennifer Beal shirt on.
- [Mike] Hi Cabot, there's
something you haven't told me.
Quite a lot.
Who are you?
- [Actor] My name is Cabot.
- [Tom] Cabot?
- [Actor] Cabot!
- [Actor] Cabot?
- [Mike] Nope,
doesn't ring a bell.
- [Actor] I'm
looking for Marlenus.
- [Mike] Marlenus' castle
is just down the road,
follow the road.
- [Tom] Strut,
pout, point it out,
what you want from me?
- [Crow] Whoa-ho
that's real butt!
- [Watney] I'm with
him, we're like this.
- [Mike] It's like being
welcome by the cast of Fame.
- [Tom] Harvey, must you
always bring your work home
from the office?
- [Actor] Darling,
what's the fuss?
- [Tom] Tell me
what's happening.
- [Actor] It's Cabot, he has
returned from his world to us.
- [Actor] So?
- [Actor] Cabot, Cabot, Cabot!
- [Tom] So, Cabot then, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah!
- [Actor] He defeated
Sarm, the priest of kings.
Darling, I owe him
my freedom too.
- [Crow] I can't find the
Christmas tree star anywhere.
- [Actor] Koruba would
still be in ruins my dear,
don't you understand?
- [Actor] Times have changed.
- [Actor] Oh, darling.
- [Actor] We are at peace now.
Does the man realize he
is disrupting our nation
by his little visit?
- Oh, darling.
- [Tom] Cabot, it is Cabot,
he has returned, my darling.
Cabot!
- [Mike] Oh, it's
a different Cabot.
- [Tom] Cabot!
- [Crow] I need a bigger room.
- [Tom] Hmm, she
must be a goalie.
- [Actor] Cabot.
- [Crow] So, uh,
Cabot's coming then?
- [Mike] Pretty much.
(all repeating "Cabot")
- [Tom] Personally, I think
Cabot is highly overrated.
- Cabot!
- [Tom] So our hero's
name is, what again?
- [Mike] Cabot.
- [Tom] Cabot.
- [Crow] Oh, I gotta
make dinner for Cabot.
- [Tom] It's time for
the Brutal Gourmet.
Ahh, good seasons and me.
Now to preheat the oven
and grease the pan.
- [Mike] This is my room, Lara,
no one said you
could come in here.
- [Actor] I do not
wish to be disturbed.
- [Actor] You will like it
less when you hear my news.
- [Crow] Kathie
Lee had her baby.
- [Actor] Charles Cabot
has returned to Gor.
- [Tom] To Gor, to Gor?
Oh Gor!
- [Actor] I told you you
would not be pleased.
- [Actor] That old fool.
There to meddle in my affairs.
- [Mike] Are you mad now?
- [Actor] Kill him!
- [Crow] Oh, I'll
do more than that.
- [Actor] What are
you going to do?
- [Crow] Kill him.
- [Actor] I don't know.
- [Tom] Oh the audition
isn't until tomorrow.
- [Crow]
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-die.
- [Tom] I'll set the table.
- [Crow] Ahh, the book says
the dove should come out now.
Crap!
- [Mike] Huh, well the Cabot
thing has really died down.
- [Actor] Cabot.
- [Cabot] My friend.
(coughing)
Oh, Professor Watney
Smith from my world.
- [Watley] My pleasure.
Yeah, sure.
- [Crow] Annoying
in any dimension.
(singing)
- [Actor] Cabot, Cabot!
- [Tom] Did you bring my pants?
(laughing)
- Oh, I'm so glad you returned.
- [Tom] Oh no, go easy there.
Dismount.
- My God, you're so beautiful
- Don't tell me, you two
know each other, right?
- Yes.
(groaning)
- [Crow] You dislocated
his mandible.
- I've been waiting
for this day.
- [Tom] Since this morning.
- Come on.
- [Mike] That guy's a
professional third wheel.
- Marlenus.
- [Tom] Wow.
- Welcome back, Cabot.
Meet my wife, Lara, the queen.
- [Tom] The trophy queen.
- [Crow] Watch out
for the tongue.
- And Xenos, the high priest.
- [Tom] Yeah, he is
pretty high up there.
- [Crow] You know him?
- My friend, Watney Smith.
- Hello.
- Tall.
(singing)
- Would you please come?
- [Tom] This is up first.
- [Crow] The world's first
successful paper mache village.
- [Tom] Fortunately this
is the land of Diary Queen.
- [Crow] Cause I can
see your Dairy Barn.
- [Mike] What do you guys
do around here for fun?
- [Tom] For some reason they're
really into Pictionary here.
(singing)
- [Cabot] Yeah,
this is the life.
- [Crow] For you maybe,
not for the women.
- [Tom] This is what I want
the inside of my
van to look like.
- [Tom] Smell this,
what's it smell like?
(groaning)
You're so tight.
- Oh yeah, Kor-u-ba.
- [Crow] Next time you
think you're romantic,
think of that guy.
- [Tom] It's Dance Party USA!
- [Crow] Hey, great floors!
Look, they're all
built like whip-its.
Whip it good.
- [Tom] You know, liturgical
dance is really weird
but it brings in
the parishioners.
- [Mike] Oh, you got that right.
- [Tom] Thank God for the pump.
- [Crow] You know I
think this is where
Denny Terrio makes his entrance.
(singing)
- [Mike] Yeah, they got pretty
decent chicken fingers here.
- [Crow] Pelvis lady
moves into position.
- [Tom] Melanie Griffith, wow!
- [Crow] So this is
Bishop's Buff-eteria.
- [Tom] Hi, we
saved you a table.
- [Crow] She's really
overdressed for this culture.
- [Tom] I've dreamed of holding
you in my arms once more.
- [Mike] Yeah, look,
we've got to order.
The kitchen closes at 10.
- [Actor] I've missed you so.
- [Crow] Hey, it's
Jeanine from Spinal Tap.
(singing)
- [Tom] Why did I
come as a cardinal?
- My darling, you
are not eating.
- [Crow] I ate last year.
- I've simply been preoccupied.
It is truly a time
of great celebration.
- I'm so glad to see
Marlenus happy again.
- [Tom] Oh cripes, you
don't know the half of it.
- You don't seem
very happy about it.
- Thank you, darling.
- [Crow] I better go say
hello to the Petersons.
(singing)
- [Tom] You have to
stop the insanity.
(doors closing)
- Mike, we admire you immensely.
- Why, thank you.
- And it's due almost entirely
to your acting career.
- Yes, well I have.
- Must be some great memories.
- You mentioned Hamlet.
- Mike, do us a favor and
lead us through those memories
with the help of this scrapbook
we found under your bed.
- Oh, you did find it, great.
This is old stuff, nobody
would be interested in this.
- Come on.
- They're old production stills.
- Bring it in.
- What's the first
one there, Mike?
- Well this first
one is HMS Pinafore.
- [Crow] Cute sailor suit.
- [Mike] I'm the lovable
Stewpot in South Pacific there.
- [Tom] Oh, that's marvelous.
- [Mike] Here's Anything
Goes Billy Crocker.
Oh, the musical Moby Dick.
- [Tom] A lot of sailor
suits early in your career.
- [Mike] There's
Death of a Salesman.
And Hair of the Wind.
Waiting for Godot.
That was a very good Godot.
There's the Hamlet.
- [Crow] That's Hamlet?
- [Mike] Yeah,
you see the skull?
Moon River anthology.
Night Wander, great production.
Murder in a Cathedral.
- [Crow] Mike, Mike, Mike.
- What?
- You're always
in a sailor suit.
- Always.
- Holy cow, I am in
sailor suit a lot.
- Well you look good
in a sailor suit.
- But how did this happen?
- Well don't worry about it.
- Well sailor suits
are comfortable, right?
- Certainly sailors
seem to like it.
- Well, yeah.
- Wilshire the Third, I'm
in a sailor suit there.
Oh Calcutta.
- Whoa, that's naughty.
- What?
- No, don't look at that.
That's not for you.
(chattering)
We'll be right back.
(adventurous music)
- [Tom] Can't explain
it, I don't know.
- Something about
Lara I don't like.
- [Tom] What's not to like?
(growling)
- [Crow] Look at my
split-top, butter-top hat.
- Those priest kings
are very dangerous.
- [Tom] Especially
with them hats.
- They have unknown powers.
- [Actor] Our honored
guest has no drink.
- Your highness.
- [Tom] Your hotness.
- So, Watley Smith, does
our world please you?
- Oh, extremely.
- [Tom] He looks
like a happy pig.
- Especially when
I'm in the company
of such a beautiful
and charming queen.
- [Crow] This is as far as
he's ever gotten with a woman.
- You and Cabot, are
you very friendly?
- [Tom] Well, we see each other.
- We teach at the same school.
- Hey, I came from far
away for your smile.
- [Tom] I have a
brain, you know.
Have you tried Denise's
cream puffs yet?
- Enjoy yourself, son.
- [Tom] Oh, hi Rick, don't.
- [Crow] And step
and spin and down.
- [Tom] And I'm down, I'm
supposed to be down, I'm sorry.
Let's clear the floor for
volleyball now, come on.
- [Crow] Now I'll coronate
the ding-a-ling sisters.
- Tonight, we have a
very special vintage.
- [Crow] 19-me.
- Bring on the wine.
- [Crow] Whoa, the keg!
It's an '83 Pat Paulsen.
- [Actor] Up!
- [Tom] Oh, I love the way
Edgar Winter opens his show.
(laughing)
- [Crow] Don't crush that
dwarf, hand me those pliers.
- There's wine in
the other barrel.
- [Actor] Hahaha, pour the wine.
- [Tom] Come pour the midgets.
- [Actor] Hey, my friend.
- [Tom] I love the hair.
- Miss me?
- [Crow] Now you
have to kiss me.
- Listen, don't think we
can't live without you.
- [Crow] Jeez, you
need some time alone?
- Cabot of the earth,
a man who one day
could be the new king of Koruba.
A toast!
- [Tom] Let's bring him out.
- To Koruba!
(cheering)
- To the new king!
- [Tom] That means I get to
be director of communications.
Meet the new boss,
same as the old boss.
- [Crow] That's a jiffy-top hat.
- [Mike] Where's the
little kings room?
- Master.
- We have to talk.
- [Crow] We
desperately need pants.
- We have no more enemies.
- Your enemies and
mine are all around us.
- How could he be dangerous
if Marlenus is king?
- [Mike] Now which
old guy are you?
- Xenos power, and
she controls Marlenus.
- [Crow] Marlenus De-trick-us?
- [Guard] I have
gate watch tonight.
- [Tom] I like Wade, he's
just not a dancer, let's go.
- I needed you sooner.
but the plans were not
in the proper position.
- [Crow] Your pants?
- Then I summoned
you through the power
of the home stone.
- [Mike] The home stone, huh?
- Protect the throne.
And the freedom of
the people of Koruba
and the home stone.
You will inherit my powers.
- You will always guide me.
- [Crow] Touch me again, you
pull back a bloody stump, kid.
- You will guide me.
- Yes, of course.
- [Tom] $200 a day plus
expenses, naturally.
Maybe we should keep
interviewing for
this king position.
- [Crow] My, my,
my, my Mitchell.
- [Tom] Who's leg is that?
This weekend package, it
was a great idea, honey.
- [Mike] That was love
of an epic proportion.
- [Crow] Let's watch Letterman.
- [Tom] Honey, could you
shovel over a little?
I don't have a lot of room here.
- [Crow] First we baste him
in real creamery butter.
(clapping)
- [Tom] Deep in
the heart of Texas.
- Tell me Watney,
would you like to
share my power with me?
- [Tom] Oh Jeez, she's trying
to sleep her way to the bottom.
- If I stay as wife to Marlenus,
the kingdom will
decend to Talena.
And from the way things look,
she'll be joined by
that fool, Cabot.
- [Crow] He's been marinated.
- He's, he's, he's
an absolute fool.
- True, true but you.
- [Mike] I think even that
guy's bones are fleshy.
- Mmm, you can be a master.
- Are you making me an offer?
- Tell me, how do they
make love on your planet?
Is it very different from ours?
- [Tom] Well I'm speaking
hypothetically, of course.
- I would like to find out.
- So would I.
- [Tom] Mmm, you smell
like comic books.
- [Crow] It's over.
- Well okay, I've
made up my mind.
I'm gonna ask her
tonight to marry me.
- Tonight?
- [Crow] Help me
choose my trousseau.
- Do you think she will accept?
- I don't know, she's
really something, isn't she?
- [Crow] She's got hams?
- Yeah, marriage, I don't know,
but I love her, I really do.
- [Tom] Whoa, a woman
could sublet that hat.
- Aren't there some
kind of rituals?
I mean, hey, she's a princess.
- You're right, she's
a princess, but.
- Why don't you ask the king?
- [Crow] I don't want
to marry the king.
- Good idea.
- [Tom] I'm starting
early today,
a little something I
call the Ramos Fizz,
I think you'll like it.
It's the Windex that
really spices it up.
- [Crow] Dearly beloved.
Some plain old dry
ice for effect.
Hey, I thought you
quit smoking, hahaha.
- [Tom] Here, now take
this out to table seven.
- [Crow] Hey, her belly
button's blinking.
- [Tom] And garnish
with a dagger.
Come on, order up!
(evil laughing)
T.G.I. Die Day.
- [Tom] No thanks, hey are my
calamari coming along here?
Here you go, Socretes.
- [Actor] To us.
- [Crow] Hmm, a lot of paperwork
in the other dimension.
(coughing)
- [Tom] Sorry, getting
a hairball there.
- [Crow] Nope, nope,
don't feel a thing, sorry.
Hmm, nuh-uh, sorry.
- [Tom] Now maybe if
you wore something sexy.
- [Crow] So how did that cost?
Wait, she's got a
denim house dress on.
- [Tom] Looks good.
- [Crow] Sheer energy.
Oh, ho, ho, that was great.
Hey, you spilled
on the great floor.
- [Mike] He's got some funny
ways of expressing affection.
Nice cheeks.
- Good luck, Marlenus
can be a stubborn man,
especially when it
comes to his daughter.
- [Crow] Oh, ho, ho, ho.
- Thank you, my friend,
- [Tom] For the show
that never ends.
- Marlenus.
- [Tom] I'm out here
with my little warrior.
- Marlenus?
- [Crow] Whoops, well,
maybe I'll come back later.
- Marlenus is dead!
Guards!
- [Tom] Volume, volume.
- Guards!
- [Crow] Don't make
a crack about that.
- [Tom] So would this
be a bad time to ask
if I can marry your daughter?
- [Crow] Well look,
here's your problem.
- No!
- [Tom] He always has a tantrum
when he doesn't
get his way, baby.
They're having a party.
- The king is dead!
The king is dead!
- [Crow] Oh, so you're
saying the king is dead.
- [Tom] Yep, time
to frame myself.
- [Crow] Oh, hi!
- He killed Marlenus, Guards!
- Cabot, what have you done?
- [Tom] Alright, what's
the trouble here?
- Dead, my husband,
the king is dead!
- [Crow] Your husband, my Dad.
Dad!
- You liar!
- You did this, you
murdered my father.
- That's impossible.
Lara was with me,
the whole evening.
(adventurous music)
- [Mike] Wow.
- [Crow] I'm gonna
kill me a mountain man.
Ahh, look at Jack run!
- Guards, seize him!
- Hey you know
where you're going?
- [Tom] Certainly!
You know they're gonna
hot roller her to death.
Are we still in the shat?
(singing)
- You know they could
claim dimensional immunity.
Bitch.
You can't kill me, I quit.
- I thought he was dead.
- Put your weapons down.
- [Tom] I didn't say Simon says.
I have never disobeyed an order.
But now I must, this
man saved our city.
Justice must be done,
out of our way, old man.
- [Crow] Hey that's
Jack Palance.
- I won't leave you
- The Gods will never harm me.
Go!
- You must be safe for Talana
and the people of Koruba, go!
Go get Cabot.
- [Tom] I'm just an intern.
- [Crow] I'll do
everything myself, there.
- Now, go get Cabot.
- [Mike] Open season
on geriatrics?
- They moved the barbie.
- [Crow] Get me a club
soda on that stand.
- [Tom] Oh, now don't
run with a knife,
it's not worth it, Cabot!
Now it's too late, they've
escaped into the soybeans.
- I'll get the hunter.
- [Crow] Hey, can
we have sex again?
(grunting)
- [Mike] Alright, woman.
- [Crow] Get him, girlfriend!
- [Tom] Now return the candy
and apologize to
the store manager.
- Let me out of here!
- [Tom] I get one call
to my tanning booth.
I should've paid those tickets.
(crying)
- [Watney] Boy,
this is incredible.
- [Mike] Torches everywhere!
- After so many years studying,
teaching people
about men with power.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm,
really, oh, neat.
- Now, if those
fools like Napoleon
and Hitler could do it,
why not Watney Smith?
King Watney, I love
it, King Watney.
What's the matter?
This is a great moment for me.
- [Tom] Look, I really
like doing stuff
but I think we should
just be friends, bye.
- Get your hands off me,
what is this, a joke?
Lara, I'm the future king!
- [Crow] This breeze.
- [Mike] Cut away!
Oh no, cut.
- That's it, you're
gonna lose your heads.
I'm warning you, I'm
going to count to three.
One, two, help!
- [Crow] Kill him.
- Oh no, they're on
the Moon Zero Two set.
- [Tom] I thought so.
The littlest buffalo
shot of them all.
- You know, I'm really
concerned about Talana.
- Don't worry, the elder
will take care of her.
- Yeah, the elder.
- [Mike] Meanwhile
I'm high and dry.
- We can't let Lara and
Xeno get away with this.
- [Tom] It just makes me so mad.
- We need to find some
help, some friends.
- Sure, like your friend Watney.
- [Mike] That hurt,
little sidekick.
- Where's the nearest town?
- [Crow] This dimension
used to be fun.
- That way.
But it's too far,
we'll never make it.
- Any alternatives?
Come on.
- [Tom] But the bus
comes by in an hour.
- No way, it's too dangerous.
I'm not walking in the dark.
- [Tom] See it's dark
there and there, dark.
- Cabot, Cabot!
- [Tom] Watch out for snakes.
- [Crow] Be loinclothed.
- How much further do
you think we have to go?
- Couple hours, more or less.
- [Tom] Hot.
Tired.
Did you catch Acalpulco
Heat last night?
- Need some help?
- [Crow] Will you carry me?
- [Tom] We could use some
roomy, button-fly Levis.
- [Crow] Hey, now
they're the same height.
- [Mike] I know, I
know, don't even say it.
- [Crow] They use
him to open oil cans.
- [Tom] I think he got that
at a rummage sale
at Jack Palance's.
- [Crow] Boing!
- Your highness, the hunter.
- [Mike] Ooh, Fred Dreyer.
- [Tom] Man, is he
over-accessorized.
- [Crow] Watch your clearance.
- [Tom] Uh, I think it's
your line, it's your line.
- [Crow] Get your butt in here.
- [Tom] Excuse me, sir, I'll
have to check your package.
It's big.
- We've all heard of you,
said to be the finest
man-hunter on Gor.
What do you have to
say for yourself?
- I'm not dead yet.
- [Crow] I'm feeling better.
- There's a prisoner
loose in the desert.
And I want him back alive.
Bring him to me.
And you shall
receive 50,000 tarts.
Dead, nothing!
- [Tom] Wounded, we can prorate
it, we'll talk about that.
Well, I guess I'll
just invoice you then.
- [Crow] He's neat.
- The hunter is
hungry, like an animal.
- [Mike] That dress
makes Jack look hippie.
- Now, how should we dispose
of the pathetic Talana?
- [Crow] Take her door
off, put her in the alley?
- [Tom] My seed pot is opening.
- What about a contest?
- [Tom] Oh, for fun!
- [Crow] Pinky Tuscadero?
- She dies.
- The guards, not I,
will determine her fate.
- [Tom] Back at ya.
- You are wise, Xeno.
- [Tom] I live to serve
you, your legginess.
- I remember, but I do not
like to be given orders.
(adventurous music)
- Say, fellas, there sure is
a lot of skin in this movie,
isn't there?
- There sure is.
- Yet despite all the
acres in question,
this film, I just can't come
up with a word to describe it.
- Well I can.
- You can?
- Why, sure.
♪ It's breastica-boobical,
chestica-mammical ♪
♪ Pendular, globular fun ♪
♪ Fleshical, orbital,
moundular-scoopular? ♪
♪ Right oh, that's the one ♪
♪ Is it glutial-maximal,
tushital-crackular ♪
♪ Bunular, morning til night? ♪
♪ Well, you're
abso-to-glandular,
fanny fantastical ♪
♪ Master-ca-fleshular right ♪
♪ It's an arealogical,
autoerotical, toobular
boobular joy ♪
♪ An exposular-regional,
batchical-pouchular ♪
♪ Fun for girl and boy ♪
♪ A latissimal-dorsical,
hung-like-a-horsical, ♪
♪ Calipyligical ball! ♪
♪ The most bunular-funular ♪
♪ Fruit-of-the-loomular ♪
♪ Frenchical-tongular ♪
♪ Wabitaboobular ♪
♪ Pendular-funular,
fruit-of-the-loomular ♪
♪ Frenchical-tongular,
wabitaboobular ♪
♪ Chestaka-orbital,
smorgastiboobular ♪
♪ Tushita-ticular ball, hey ♪
- Hey guys, how's the movie?
♪ Oh, it's breastica-boobical,
chestica-mammical ♪
♪ Pendular, globular fun ♪
(doors opening)
(laughing)
- [Tom] Blobula, boobula.
- [Mike] Hey look, the Judds.
- [Crow] Hey
God, I'm drunk.
- [Mike] Well, they've got
their mudflaps on, that's good.
- [Crow] Dirty pictures
of guys on them.
- [Tom] Oh, this is like
interactive wrestling.
- [Crow] Joan Fontaine
and Olivia de Havilland
in a fight to the death.
- [Tom] Wow.
- [Mike] I think
all this infighting
is really hurting the National
Organization of Women.
- [Crow] Whoa.
Okay, okay, you can
borrow my shirt,
just don't fit it out.
- [Tom] Lambada,
the forbidden dance.
- [Crow] Must be sweeps week.
Wow, these Tupperware parties
are getting way out of hand.
- [Tom] Camille Bowie
and Susan Faludi,
the final conflict.
- [Crow] Let's just
agree to disagree, okay?
- [Tom] Mike, will
you make me my own
jack-booted dominatrix.
- [Mike] No.
- [Crow] Whoa, thanks, Susan.
I don't need your help.
- [Tom] Wonder woman.
(singing)
Oh, she'll be out
for the season.
- Take her away!
- [Mike] Get her more oil.
- [Tom] What about me?
- [Queen] That little
fighting bird must die.
- [Crow] And take that hat off.
- [Xeno] Why not
wait till your caged.
- Has Cabot been captured?
- Do not be too eager
to have your revenge.
- Why not?
Am I not queen?
- [Crow] Ain't I a woman?
- Don't challenge me.
- There are still
those in Koruba
who would have another in
your place on the throne.
- Let them dare try.
- [Tom] Whoops,
misplayed my hand there.
- [Crow] Oh yeah?
Iraq is doom, desert
planet, the long version.
- [Mike] I wonder what
Billy Body would do
in this situation.
- [Crow] Wake up, ya big load.
- [Tom] Boy, I could
go for a short stack.
- [Crow] You do him well.
- Let's move, we won't last
another day without water.
- [Crow] Say, last
night did I, nevermind.
- [Mike] Hey that's where
Fred Flintstone works.
- [Tom] Another nice day!
- Come on, this way.
- [Crow] Okay, I'll
just follow your butt.
Well, not anymore I won't.
- [Tom] Midday at the oasis.
- [Mike] Ahh, I'm
getting sand in my socks.
- [Tom] Yeah, well I'm
chaffing like a bear.
- [Crow] Which way
is Judy Jetson?
- Look, water.
- [Tom] It don't look like much,
but if you wanna hit the big
jacks this is the place to go.
- [Crow] Silver spoon.
- [Tom] Damn it, Cabot, this
is not your personal war!
- Cabot, no, Cabot,
stop, it's poison.
- How do you know?
- [Crow] And your point?
- [Tom] In the desert, you
don't remember your name.
- [Crow] That's funny,
you're starting to look
more like Joey
Heatherton all the time.
- That mountain over there.
I saw that mountain yesterday.
- [Crow] It's
clearly following us.
- I'm sure.
We're walking a circle.
- [Tom] Oh, good one, Cabot.
- Look, slavers.
- [Crow] Uh oh, warrior
of the lost world.
(singing)
- [Tom] Hold my arm.
Whoa, that's not my arm.
- [Crow] They're
going downhill fast.
- [Mike] Oh you're
right, they are.
(singing)
- [Crow] I've figured it out.
That guy's the photo negative
of Herve Villechaize.
I bet he won a lot
of limbo contests.
Well, in his class.
(singing)
Boy, we got good seats, huh?
- [Tom] The first Lollapalooza.
(coughing)
- [Crow] Now did
I get this right?
I'm supposed to come
out to the desert
and beat the crap out of people?
- [Tom] Come on, you're
watching Chevy Chase
whether you like it or not.
- [Crow] Did you boof?
- Marlenus' goal
is to end slavery.
- [Tom] Yeah, I know.
- Lara obviously has
no such intention.
- [Mike] Yeah, I see.
- [Crow] Well, I'm
glad we had this talk.
Whoa, they're jumping
right in the boat there.
Hey, no fair, you're caught,
you have to stay in the middle.
You too.
- [Tom] Hey, give me a
hand, I'm swamped here.
- [Crow] It's the S&M follies.
He's down at the
40, he's up again.
- [Tom] You know the
slaves were the underdogs
at the beginning of this season.
- [Mike] Look at,
she's laughing.
- [Crow] You've got
spunk, I hate spunk.
- [Tom] Well it looks
like it's almost over,
let's get to our car
and beat the traffic.
- [Crow] You think I
look like Greg Norman?
- Let's go, they have water.
- I'm not so sure I
want to end up a slave.
- Listen, as long as I have
some blood left in my veins,
I will always fight
slavery and oppression.
- [Crow] Starting tomorrow.
The whole halter top thing
just isn't happening for him.
- [Tom] Why are they wearing
toilet lids on their necks?
- [Crow] Now I'm gonna save him.
(groaning)
This movie is for the ladies.
- [Tom] But I like it too.
- [Crow] You saw my
butt, didn't you?
- [Tom] Hey, you
seen macaroni yet?
I've heard it's excellent.
Let's catch it and then
go for some espresso.
- [Mike] Now somebody left
a perfectly good slave here.
- [Cabot] They left
this one to die.
- [Crow] Well, he's
good for parts.
- [Tom] Oh look, his
eyeball comes right out.
- He's dead.
- There's nothing we can do.
- [Tom] Except play with him.
- [Mike] Ow, jeez,
I was marching.
I was in line!
Oh, yeah, pick me up, grab
me, that's good, that's great.
- [Crow] And so the Osmonds
are marched from the top.
- [Tom] Oh, you know
these slavers are so mean.
You know it doesn't take
any more time to be nice.
- [Mike] No, did it
ever occur to them
that you can catch more
slaves with kindness?
- [Crow] Oh, that's right,
you can catch more
slaves with honey
than you can with vinegar.
- [Mike] Absolutely.
- [Tom] Check it out,
one of them Jack Nicklaus
golf communities.
- [Mike] Are you old?
How do you know about that?
Let's watch them from
a different angle.
Yep, they're still slaves.
- [Actor] Well the best
metal on the market
would be two stalls
on the right hand side
opposite the stand.
- Thank you.
- [Actor] It's a pleasure,
you wanna buy some meat?
- No, no.
- [Tom] Look, shut up.
- [Actor] Meat, fresh meat!
- Cabot, you want some?
- [Crow] Thanks, daddy-o.
- No, thanks I'm vegetarian.
- [Tom] Yeah, no problem.
Hey, you gonna pay for
that apple, hot shot?
- [Crow] Great slave
in a wooden cage.
- [Auctioneer] So what do I got
for this piece of merchandise?
25, 25, I got 25.
- [Crow] Nah, we can get
her cheaper at a Midway.
- [Mike] What's
your captor like?
- [Crow] I have come to chew
bubble gum and kick ass,
and I'm all out of ass.
Hello.
- [Tom] Try the apples.
- [Crow] Do you have a Camaro?
Hi, thanks for
coming around today.
I see your horns
are upside down.
Oh, thank you, that's
all I wanted to tell you.
They just don't
have my size here.
- [Tom] You wanna maybe
just go to the food court?
I need a baked
potato or something.
- Sooner or later they're going
to spot us in these clothes.
- [Crow] What clothes?
You're wearing a leather thong.
- [Tom] I'm sneaky.
(singing)
- [Crow] Oh, haha,
this is going to be
like Bosom Buddies, isn't it?
- [Mike] Is Wendy
Jo Sperber in this?
- [Crow] Who?
Hey, girlfriend.
- You pay for this?
You thief.
- [Crow] I love you.
Well they have towels,
now they need costumes.
(grumbling)
- [Mike] Hey, leave her alone.
(groaning)
- What are you doing
with the merchandise?
- [Crow] But the
merchandise started it.
Hey, check this,
la-la-la-la-la-la.
- [Mike] Knock that off, please.
- [Crow] Say, it really
brings out his eyes.
Oh, God, do I feel done.
- [Tom] It's just
like electric typing.
- [Crow] I love my
job, who's next.
- Hey, you with the long hair.
- [Crow] Hey, I'm a bartender
and it's not fun anymore.
(grunting)
(babbling)
- I'll give you 150 for this.
- [Crow] Why I would.
- Look how lively she
is under these rags.
(shouting)
- [Crow] 200, is that all?
- This must stop.
- [Tom] First thing
Monday morning.
Well, another senseless
horse jacking here.
- [Mike] Hayo,
whatever your name is.
- [Crow] Babafet.
A vast matey, yeah.
- [Tom] Man, Barnaby Jones
had better fight scenes
than this movie.
Oh thank you, I'll
just stab myself here.
- [Crow] I wonder if
there were actual suicides
in this film.
- [Mike] Hi-ho, oh, I keep
forgetting my dang sidekick.
- [Crow] Well enough hot
dogging, let's get out of here.
- [Mike] Lucky for
him it was a pony.
Ooh, a rare triple.
- [Tom] Top speed, oh, too fast.
- [Crow] Oh, you could stop
and ask for
directions, you know.
- [Tom] Well, thanks for coming.
Good one, Cabot,
you just set fire
to the Boy Scout jamboree.
- [Crow] Well that pretty
much busts up the sale.
(babbling)
Permission to get
out of the fire, sir?
- [Tom] Dear friend,
you mean so much to me
in so many ways.
I know we haven't
been close lately.
You're hurting from the
hurt that is everywhere.
Hurting everyone.
Don't hurt.
- [Mike] Oh Dove
bars, I love them
no matter what dimension I'm in.
- [Crow] Boss, your
batch is on fire.
I wasn't gonna say anything but
the smell is putting me off.
- [Tom] Well, the lizards good.
God, I hate camping.
- [Crow] Did you ever
know that you're my hero.
Well, third wheel again.
Okay, I'll leave.
Really it's no bother,
no bother at all.
- [Mike] Keep going, farther.
- [Tom] Oh, you have a mole
here, it looks infected.
- [Mike] I have to request
that you not touch my butt.
- What are you doing?
- Master, allow me
to give you pleasure.
- I'm not your master.
- [Tom] You see freedom
is with the pleasure!
- You're very, very beautiful
but I'm in love
with another woman.
- Love?
- Yeah, she feels for
me and I feel for her
and we're free to express it.
- [Crow] Naked.
- And now you are free.
- A woman may be free to
feel for who she wants?
- [Tom] That's what
it says in Cosmo.
- Well, in my world it is so.
And it shall be here too.
- You are a very
strange warrior.
- [Tom] In fact you're a freak.
- Maybe, maybe.
- [Crow] What are you,
let's do it, come on.
- [Tom] Well can I just
stroke your hip again?
- [Mike] No.
- [Tom] One nipple.
- [Crow] No, no, no,
no, no pleasuring me.
Don't pleasure me.
- [Tom] Cabot.
- [Mike] Don't these
people ever floss?
Savages.
(upbeat music)
(threatening music)
- [Crow] Why thank you,
sir, that is very kind.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh, he looks like
a little angel.
- [Mike] He looks
like a gravy boat.
- [Tom] Those shoes
are very expensive.
An open toed Doc Martin.
- [Crow] Hey, I'm from
the camp across the lake,
can I borrow some sugar?
- [Tom] Yeah, yeah, cold shower.
(singing)
- [Mike] Nice job on
watch, short round.
- [Tom] So, could I
like, pleasure you now?
- [Crow] The baton nature walk.
Can we play something?
Count the rocks or.
- [Mike] It's so great we
don't have to talk, you know?
- [Tom] So, is Hunter
your real name?
- [Crow] Shut up.
- [Tom] Does hunting
stuff pay pretty good?
Are you bonded with the state?
Or is that stuff
licensed out of the.
- [Crow] She's so lucky.
- [Tom] You know this
is the kind of thing
just designed to bring
resentment in the slaves.
- [Mike] Oh man, she's
heavier than she looks.
Does she carry her coins
everywhere she goes?
- [Crow] Next kingdom
over, Nell Carter is queen.
- [Tom] Pull over now,
I desire a nut roll.
- [Crow] Hey, that looks like.
- [Mike] Hey, hey,
hey, hey, not!
- [Tom] Well, just that
I envy that structure.
- [Crow] It's Dr.
Freud's office.
- [Tom] Oh God, please
invent the battery.
All the guards are
wearing penny loafers.
- [Crow] You know you
remember to rotate your men
every 10,000 miles.
- [Tom] I think this
is a handicap space,
uh, ma'am, ma'am?
- [Crow] Finally, we're
cleaning out the basement.
- [Tom] Sampo, Sampo, Sampo.
- [Crow] Sampo!
- [Mike] Don't worry, I'm
not overworked or anything.
- Would you like a guided
tour, your highness?
- [Tom] A tour of my highness,
well you rude little man.
- All day and all night.
They don't know the difference
between sunrise and sunset.
- Good, let them learn as I did.
- [Crow] These slaves
today, I tell ya.
- What did you learn?
- Power is all.
Some are born to be whipped,
some born to rule.
- [Tom] I'll be whipped,
I'll be whipped.
(whipping)
- [Mike] Oh, the salt mines.
- [Crow] Oh, Bob Fosse.
- [Tom] Some men just
can not wear a bustier.
You never would believe it
where Keebler cookies come from.
- [Mike] Well, just a
little asbestos, men.
- [Crow] Oh, they're
making those,
there's a great need for those.
- [Mike] I think they're
mining giant Chicken McNuggets.
- The workers will be crushed.
Just feel terrible.
- [Tom] But the mines
were your life's blood.
- [Crow] These people
need a Mother Jones
or a Martha Ray.
- Wait.
- [Crow] Now go.
- But your majesty,
there's a slide.
- We've plenty more slaves
where they came from.
Send them back.
- Close the exits.
- [Mike] They're smiling,
they're all smiling.
- [Tom] Hey man, we
already punched out.
- [Crow] Now the
queen's being penny wise
and pound foolish.
There's gotta be capital costs
involved in getting more slaves.
- [Tom] Hey, is
something coming down?
- Let those who are
alive carry out the dead.
- [Tom] No other way to work it.
- You gave the order.
- I thought you would
enjoy to see me suffer
the way I now enjoy
seeing others suffer.
- [Crow] Awkward moment.
- Your highness, the
hunter has returned.
- Now go meet the hunter,
and bring me back my prize.
- [Mike] Well this is gonna
come up in labor talks.
- See the poor slaves
are sent to the mine.
The work must continue.
- [Tom] Must be a
DeBeers mountain.
- [Crow] Aww jeez,
now they need slaves
to clean up the other slaves.
- [Tom] I'd say
hundreds are dead
in a horrible mining accident.
- [Crow] No, no, no, no,
no, no comment, no comment.
- [Tom] Oh, I gotta start
sending out some resumes.
- [Crow] Sister
Mary, Jack Palance.
- The enemy of the state
no longer wants free.
Now Cabot is yours,
your majesty.
Yours, to destroy.
- [Crow] Believe it.
- I do not want him destroyed.
(mimicking)
Guards, take him to the cells.
- [Tom] First, the
sabbath prayer.
- You heard the queen.
Obey her!
Come on!
- [Crow] Don't want to be
pleasured by the slave girl,
what was I thinking?
- [Tom] Cruella de
Vil, Cruella de Vil.
- Lost.
- [Tom] Mmm, Idaho
potato, thank you.
Fill out a 1099.
- Now, are you satisfied?
- I shall never be satisfied,
till you kneel before me and
accept me fully as your queen.
- [Crow] That's all
you're looking for?
No problem!
- I am but a humble
priest, your majesty.
I kneel only before my God.
- [Mike] Oh, your
God is so good.
- [Tom] Wow, these
Steak and Ale's
get crowded on
the weekends, huh?
- [Crow] The true
story of biosphere two.
- He must be killed, he
will destroy our power.
- My power.
He's a greater threat
dead than alive.
You see how they worship him.
We must not make him a martyr.
- Dead, the people
will soon forget him.
Alive, they go.
- [Tom] I wish I
could fire priests.
- [Crow] Go, Jack, go.
(doors closing)
- [Mike] Guys, guys, guys.
- What, what, what?
- Guess what I got?
- What?
- It's Jack Palance's book on
the making of today's movie.
Palance on Palance,
Believe It Or Not.
- Cool, let me read it.
Oh, oh, let's see.
Day one, missed call.
Partied all night with
that platinum midget fellow
and albino.
Still having trouble
seeing straight.
- Okay, let's see.
Day three, missed call,
wandered into shop yesterday
and they decided to keep it.
What the heck does
Avanti Avanti mean?
- Okay, okay, okay,
day five, missed call.
After four days of shooting,
finally got script today
and guess what?
I'm not playing Thomas Aquinus,
I'm supposed to be some
kind of freaking wizard.
(laughing)
- Day eight, missed call,
just can't get canceled
series Bronk off my mind.
Why, why, can't
keep anything down.
Not sleeping.
- Let me read,
day nine, missed call.
Went to village with Gina.
My voice scares
little Italian kids.
Spent entire per diem
on bunch of crap.
- Okay, okay, okay,
day ten, missed call.
I think I killed a
man today, more later?
Jeez, Mike, I think
that's enough.
- I don't think I
want to know any more.
- Hey guys, a whole
chapter on Tango and Cash.
- We saw Russell's butt today.
(laughing)
(adventurous music)
- [Mike] Are you playing
Ringmar Game of Gor?
- Bring in the prisoner.
- [Crow] And you carry
the Wall Street Journal.
- [Tom] Stuck in a Wizard
of Id cartoon, huh?
- [Mike] Shirley, I'm ready.
- [Tom] So how was
your little stay?
Did you enjoy it?
Oh, don't forget, you've got
to sign for your phone calls.
- [Mike] Well, we expect him
any time here, your wizardness.
Oh, here he comes now.
- [Crow] Oh, Dad, thanks for
bailing me out of jail again.
Sorry about the car.
- I have come to
make a deal with you.
- [Tom] Here, taste
this, will ya?
Oh, no, wasabi, ugh.
- Enough.
- [Tom] Oh, one word, seasoning.
- What?
- [Tom] I thought you knew.
- I am prepared to
set you free, if.
- [Crow] If it's the children.
- You promise to leave Koluba
and return to your own planet.
If you give me your
word, I will let you go.
- [Tom] Yeah, yeah,
can I get a wet-nap?
- I don't deal with butchers.
- [Crow] Oh, wow.
(whip cracking)
(shouting)
- I said, no deal!
- [Mike] O-kay!
- [Crow] I brought
the wrong bowl.
- Or
- [Tom] There's a,
aww, hell, I'm lost.
- [Mike] Guacamole's off.
- [Crow] Look at that,
look what you did,
you bad, bad, shame on
you, outside, outside!
Hey could I have
a sandwich here?
- [Mike] Wow, could only
watch so much of that.
- [Crow] I mean, so
how could they preempt
Doctor Quinn Medicine
Woman two weeks in a row?
- [Tom] I'm gonna
write my affiliates.
- Ahh, there you are.
I will see Cabot now.
- [Crow] Oh please, let's
not have another vague scene.
- I would not advise
that, your excellency.
- [Tom] You want to pop over?
- And why not?
- He must remain
in solitary longer
as further punishment.
- Nonsense, guards,
get him for me.
- [Crow] Okily, dokily doo.
Uh, sorry to bother you, sir.
There's a grand
wizard to see you.
- Haven't you guys
had enough yet?
(laughing)
- [Crow] Oh, you Cabot, come on.
- [Mike] Oh, Pavarotti has
really fallen on tough times.
His art must not be selling.
- [Crow] Oh shoot, just
locked myself in, darn.
- [Tom] Aw gee,
guys, thanks a lot,
if you just point me
in the right direction
I can take it from here.
Oh, I guess not, okay.
- [Mike] I'm so ashamed.
- What have you done
to the prisoner?
- [Tom] We canceled
it, it was too obscure.
- Answer me.
- [Crow] This is
really awkward but
he didn't like Bronk.
- He was offered an
opportunity, your highness.
He refused.
He was then disciplined.
- What are you talking about?
- [Tom] I really don't know.
- What opportunity?
What did you offer him?
- [Tom] Sidekick
on Conan O'Brien?
- Freedom, your highness,
if he would only return
to his own planet.
- Freedom?
But he's my prisoner to
be handled as I so wish.
- I know.
- [Crow] Jack, Jack,
over here buddy.
- [Mike] There you go.
- Because you are behaving
like a bitch in heat,
and not like a queen.
- [Tom] Jack, you
are way off script.
- Get out of here,
you disgusting worm.
(laughing)
- Your royal highness.
- [Crow] Now if you'll excuse me
I'm going to go
tear my agent a new.
Duh, all rise for the queen.
- You're a lucky slave.
- There are no more slaves.
- In my empire, nothing else.
- [Tom] Whoa, she's on a
lazy Susan or something.
- I could've had you killed.
- [Mike] I'm sure that Xeno
picked one to do
your dirty work.
(chattering)
- Good help is hard
to find these days.
(whipping)
- [Tom] Oh, I forgot
you had the whip.
- [Crow] Get you
some chamomile tea?
- The people continue to
hold their faith in you.
I can make you their martyr.
- [Tom] Or I can
make you a margarita.
- Or I can make
you a better offer.
- Like the one
you did to Watney?
- I can show you pain.
Or I can show you pleasure.
- With you, it doesn't
make any difference.
- Do you not want me?
I can make you far
more than a slave.
- [Tom] You can be my juggler.
- I control the people and
you know that is power.
And they will only listen to me.
So why not make it easier.
You were a hero
once to the people,
I can make you a hero again.
- [Tom] Or I can
make you a fluffin'.
- Our power could be invincible
and no on would
stand in our way.
- [Crow] Can we just snuggle?
- Xeno?
- Ha, he's gone too far.
But you, you.
- [Tom] Me what?
- [Crow] Let me shoot it over
to my lawyers real quick.
- [Tom] You taste like bronzer.
- Your choice.
- Return me to my cell.
- Guards!
Then they must know
who you really are.
An alien and a murderer.
- [Crow] Ooh, I just
hit the great floors.
- Then you must confess
to the murder of Marlenus,
king of Koruba.
Confess!
- [Crow] Okay, I
ate the brownies.
I didn't know they were full of.
- [Mike] T.E. Lawrence.
One more time for T.E. Lawrence.
(whip cracking)
- [Crow] Okay, I like
noozies and swinkets.
- [Tom] I was in
Starlight Exrpess.
- [Mike] Her problem is that
she let him know she
liked him too soon.
- [Crow] Yeah, we
totally redid it in here,
you should've seen
what they had.
- [Tom] Wallpapering.
Just wanted to apologize,
bring you a fruit basket.
- Wake up.
Wake up!
- [Crow] Wake up, boss
is gone and she's mad.
Man, the forum is hell.
- [Mike] Oh, look over there.
It's the queen mother.
What a nice old gal.
- [Tom] Hey slaves,
dead old slaves.
Get 'em fast, slightly
lethargic, but still dead.
- [Crow] I can't believe
that hat was ever in style.
- [Mike] Hey, intolerance.
Sort of.
- [Crow] Hey, quick everyone,
Don McLean is up next.
Hi Raj, hi Dwayne.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Supertramp.
Dreamer, you know
you are a dreamer.
- [Mike] And now a
word from King Friday.
- [Crow] They've
captured Roxette.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Oh, she's in
black and she's outside.
Wrong, wrong.
- [Mike] Ohh, do we
have to see this?
- [Tom] Hi, hi, sorry
you had to see my butt.
(adventurous music)
- Everybody rise.
- [Crow] Here come the judge.
- [Mike] Michael J. Fox.
- [Tom] Uh, is this Paramus?
- [Mike] Hey, Sheila E relaxing.
- [Tom] Black velvet,
if you please.
- [Mike] Check out that.
Wash and go, Pert Plus.
- All kneel, Delilah,
queen of Koruba.
- [Crow] Or not, whatever's
okay with you guys.
- [Tom] Don't worry, kids.
We'll have lions
eating Christians
if you'll just be patient.
Sir, I think you'll be more
comfortable down there.
- [Crow] No, no, no, no.
Scotch, make it
a double, no ice.
- Send in the challengers.
- But first, my queen, we must
appease the spirits above.
We must drink a toast
to the gods of carnage.
- [Crow] That dude could drink
a toast when a leaf falls.
- [Mike] He made up
the gods of carnage.
- [Tom] Thanks, Mirna, nice hat.
- We shall drink.
- [Tom] The impossible drink.
- To the death of Tal and Cabot.
- I shall join you
in your prayer.
- [Crow] You're
ruining my toast.
- To the gods above, may they
bless our land, ever all.
- [Tom] Oh, what a kick.
Alright, I'm out
of the film, yes!
- To the guards, may they
last forever, forevermore.
- [Tom] I believe in Crystal
Light, because I believe in me.
Now, kill him!
- [Crow] Okay, but I just
remembered I gotta punch in.
- [Mike] Oh, I hate it when
they use a net to kill them,
it takes forever.
- [Crow] Should they start
saying Cabot, Cabot, Cabot.
- [Tom] Runners take
your marks, or not.
- [Mike] That's not him,
good thing they brought
his stunt double in.
- [Crow] Yeah, but
he fights good.
Too bad he wasn't the hero.
- [Mike] No need to worry,
it's all part of the act.
Well, that wasn't.
- [Tom] Oh, hey, you've got
bits of dolphin in that net.
- [Crow] These people should
invent vaudeville or something.
- [Tom] Oh, not in the sand.
Right in the sand.
- [Crow] Hey, mock with
the queen's very rules.
Alright, there,
you'll keep them.
- [Mike] Does he really
need the eye makeup?
What does this clown
have against dirt?
- [Mike] Ted Danson.
- Stop him.
- [Crow] Oh, great, just
when Sir Chants-a-lot
is done in the micro.
Alright, come on.
- [Tom] Oh crap,
here come our Dads.
- [Crow] Clear, live
damn it, come on!
- [Tom] Everyone grab your oh!
Oh, wow.
- Kill him, send in the hunter.
- [Mike] Oh, hi, sorry I'm
late, there was this thing.
- [Queen] Kill him!
- Stop!
Your queen Lara is the assassin.
Lara killed Marleuns.
- Kill him!
- It's true.
Lara killed Marlenus.
- Do as I did, kill him.
He speaks lies.
- [Crow] And kill yourselves.
Kill everyone.
- [Tom] Should I?
Aww, what the hell.
(laughing)
- [Crow] Cry Freedom
Two, the Armageddon.
- [Tom] Goodnight, now.
Now we need another
hot chick to worship.
- [Crow] Give it
up for your posse!
- [Mike] Now here
comes the hard part
because with freedom
comes responsibility.
- [Crow] She's cheeky!
- [Tom] And thus ended
the patch of crusades.
- [Mike] Mmm, these
candles are good.
- This time, Tarl Cabot,
I'm not gonna let
you get away from me.
- I won't leave you anymore.
I promise.
- [Crow] Let's see too.
- There's no such
plans as surrendering.
(groaning)
- Don't worry about him.
- What's it like to be king?
- [Tom] It's good
to be the king.
- It's a responsibility.
- You and I can
take responsibility.
- [Tom] Open wide.
- [Crow] Oh, he looks
like a large mouth bass
going after an injured
minnow or something.
- [Tom] Someone is calling.
- [Crow] Lonnie, did you
close all the time portholes?
- Cabot?
- [Mike] Oh, no,
he's stuck in the,
that's like the delightful
cherry on top of this movie.
- [Crow] Oh my.
- Where the hell am I?
- [Crow] You're the hell here.
- [Tom] There, Italian
actors pretending to be
gay American cops.
- Where am I?
I can not believe this.
- [Crow] This guy
is disoriented.
Let's go find your Daddy.
- [Mike] I don't know, I think
a little spell in the hoosgow
might just be the
thing this guy needs.
- [Crow] Might be perfect.
- [Mike] Oh, my New York town.
- [Crow] Isn't this just
typical of wherever this is?
You know, actually, I
think this is Italy.
- [Tom] No, during this shot
there have been
three governments.
Italy!
- [Crow] You know, to my taste
there wasn't enough of
that guy in the movie,
I say pile on more of him.
- [Mike] You know they
haven't stopped that tape
because the guy was
cracking up the crew.
- [Crow] Really?
- [Mike] Oh no, the crew
actually rushed over
and beat the crap out of him.
- [Crow] Yeah, that's
what I thought.
- [Mike] Ahh, well.
- [Crow] Have you seen the
outtakes for this film?
- [Mike] No, why,
do they show them
on Bloopers and Practical Jokes?
- [Crow] No, Faces
of Death actually.
- [Mike] Sounds like Miami Vice.
- [Crow] Say, do
you think this movie
was ever released
in the theaters?
- [Mike] No, I don't think so,
but there's a good bet it
was on the USA Network.
- [Tom] Oh, the USA.
(singing)
I really like the original
movies they've made,
especially for the USA Network.
(singing)
- [Mike] Yeah, they're great.
And they all seem to have
titles like Malibu Death Breast
or Jeff Conway and
Shari Belafonte Harbor
play a deadly game
of cat and mouse
in Murder Most Moist.
- [Crow] Oh, hey, let
me play, I got one.
Judy Landers is on the trail
of a devious killer in
Peekabo Lace, P.I.
Oh wait, how about Jeff
Conway is a vigilante
who stalks by night
in Dark Underpants.
- [Mike] How about this one?
Lindsay Wagner is a
sexy speech therapist
held hostage in Tongue Lashing.
- [Crow] Hold it, hold
it, hold it, I got it,
how about Jeff Conway is
up to his mouth in murder
in French Pistol.
- [Mike] Catch it.
- [Tom] This is fun.
- [Mike] Okay, here,
try and top this one.
Jeff Conway is a
college professor
who's secret life catches
up with him in Death Spank.
- [Tom] Oh, good
one, Death Spank.
- [Crow] Oh, I got a good one.
How about Chris Lemon
and Heather Locklear
form a crime-fighting unit
in the Lingerie Justice Files.
- [Tom] That's good,
I've got another.
Jeff Conway and Morgan Fairchild
are the Crotch-less Killers.
- [Crow] I like it, I like.
It's got verb.
Or how about Hard Buckner
weaves a wind of suspicion
between Richard
Chamberlain and Ben Vereen
in Tap Pant Desire.
- [Mike] I like
the way you think.
Try this one on.
William Devane tracks a
killer in a tropical paradise
in the Hawaii Edible
Underwear Murders.
- [Tom] Mike, I love
you for that one.
Okay, get this.
Lisa Hartman is a streetwise cop
who traps a killer
in Cheek Beats.
- [Mike] Now Servo,
I'd marry you for that.
Oh, I have one,
this one's great.
Jeff Conway is a
crazed cult leader
in the Waco Panty Raid.
Eric Roberts is a
freaked out artist
who gets more than
he bargained for
in Naked Came The Nude.
- [Tom] Peter Deluise and
Tommy Tune are Cod Police.
(laughing)
(triumphant music)
(doors closing)
- Fact, in this movie alone
there were more groin shots
of the human male body
than I all previously
viewed movies combined.
- With that in mind.
- Let's watch.
(upbeat music)
- Think about it, won't you.
- Thank you, well, sirs.
(piano music)
(upbeat music)
(spooky music)
(triumphant music)
- Get out of here,
you disgusting worm.